<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment Strategy on Siyao(Heidi) Yuan</title>
    <link>https://ysyheidi.github.io/tags/investment-strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment Strategy on Siyao(Heidi) Yuan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ysyheidi.github.io/tags/investment-strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Investment Strategy in China’s Financial Market</title>
      <link>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/12/investment-strategy-in-chinas-financial-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/12/investment-strategy-in-chinas-financial-market/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We decided to choose individual investors. Because we think it’s more practical and feasible for us who are short of real investment experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client is a middle-aged woman with $500,000 (RMB 3,100,000) to invest. She is relatively a risk lover. With Chinese stock market booming, she wants to invest in the stock market. Her expected return is 15% in one year and the maximum loss she can afford is 20%. Our target is to maximize the profit while controlling the risk by diversifying the investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we decided to construct a portfolio with high return and high risk, we choose to invest 80% in the stock market. Meanwhile, we use the investment in bond market (20%) to reduce the risk to some degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For stock investment, we first choose four stable and promising industries according to Chinese government policies, which are construction, finance, environmental protection and alternative energy. Then we construct a scoring system according to the method of Analytic Hierarchy Process (AHP) as well as the growth and risk factors. This is a system that will score the stocks based on the weight of each factor, and then at the beginning of each quarter, we will buy and hold the portfolio with highest scores. Each quarter the portfolio will be adjusted in terms of new scores at each quarter. We use this system to pick 5 stocks with highest scores in each of the four industries to construct our stock portfolio. To determine the weights of the selected 20 stocks, we use mean-variance optimization method. In addition, we choose Chinese one year T-bills as our risk-free asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the evaluation part, we find our whole portfolio with 19.446% return in the two months which beat the benchmark, but when compared to individual industry stock portfolio, our stock investment has inferior return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>