<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Siyao(Heidi) Yuan</title>
    <link>https://ysyheidi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Siyao(Heidi) Yuan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ysyheidi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Sloan</title>
      <link>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/12/hello-sloan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/12/hello-sloan/</guid>
      <description>Three passions, simple but overwhelmingly strong, have governed my life: the longing for love, the search for knowledge, and unbearable pity for the suffering of mankind. --Three Passions I have Lived For, by Bertrand Russell</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payout Policy Research of Kweichow Maotai Co., Ltd</title>
      <link>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/12/payout-policy-research-of-kweichow-maotai-co.-ltd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/12/payout-policy-research-of-kweichow-maotai-co.-ltd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This paper intends to research into the chosen company-- Kweichow Maotai Co., Ltd about its characteristics which entitle it to be the leading firm in the white spirit industry within China. Based its general conditions, this paper mainly focus on its capital structure with very leverage ratio and very high liquidity ratio of debt and asset, as well as its payout policy which returns relatively small amount of cash compared to its price back to the investors. Simultaneously we also take the interest conflicts and the competitive scenario with other rivals into consideration. It can be concluded that the financial response of its leverage level and dividend policy is not significant. While the major suggestions given from this paper contend that it should raise more debt when faced with worthwhile investing projects and should increase the dividend yield ratio for the feedback of its investors, which can also reduce its excess cash at hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Determinants of Credit Spread on Corporate Bonds: Based on Observations of China’s Market</title>
      <link>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/12/determinants-of-credit-spread-on-corporate-bonds-based-on-observations-of-chinas-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/12/determinants-of-credit-spread-on-corporate-bonds-based-on-observations-of-chinas-market/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Theoretically, the fair value of a bond is the present value of the stream of cash flows that are expected to generate. Hence, the value of the bond is obtained by discounting the bond’s expected cash flow to the present using an appropriate discount rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commercial Bank Competition and Risk --Empirical study on 20 non-OECD countries</title>
      <link>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/11/commercial-bank-competition-and-risk---empirical-study-on-20-non-oecd-countries/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/11/commercial-bank-competition-and-risk---empirical-study-on-20-non-oecd-countries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is a hotspot for economists to discuss and reflect the relationship between risks and competition. Till now there is no consensus among researchers. With the unbalanced panel data of all commercial banks in 20 non-OECD countries over 2000-2014, the article tried to figure out the relationship between competition and risk. Time variant Competition was measured by the Panzar-Rosse H statistics and risk was measured by rolling Z-scores. In the final regression, other macroeconomic index and bank specific factors were considered. Results found that banks` risks level would increase with the increase of market competition while a relatively larger bank would be less impacted by competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investment Strategy in China’s Financial Market</title>
      <link>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/10/investment-strategy-in-chinas-financial-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2018/10/investment-strategy-in-chinas-financial-market/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We decided to choose individual investors. Because we think it’s more practical and feasible for us who are short of real investment experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client is a middle-aged woman with $500,000 (RMB 3,100,000) to invest. She is relatively a risk lover. With Chinese stock market booming, she wants to invest in the stock market. Her expected return is 15% in one year and the maximum loss she can afford is 20%. Our target is to maximize the profit while controlling the risk by diversifying the investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we decided to construct a portfolio with high return and high risk, we choose to invest 80% in the stock market. Meanwhile, we use the investment in bond market (20%) to reduce the risk to some degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For stock investment, we first choose four stable and promising industries according to Chinese government policies, which are construction, finance, environmental protection and alternative energy. Then we construct a scoring system according to the method of Analytic Hierarchy Process (AHP) as well as the growth and risk factors. This is a system that will score the stocks based on the weight of each factor, and then at the beginning of each quarter, we will buy and hold the portfolio with highest scores. Each quarter the portfolio will be adjusted in terms of new scores at each quarter. We use this system to pick 5 stocks with highest scores in each of the four industries to construct our stock portfolio. To determine the weights of the selected 20 stocks, we use mean-variance optimization method. In addition, we choose Chinese one year T-bills as our risk-free asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the evaluation part, we find our whole portfolio with 19.446% return in the two months which beat the benchmark, but when compared to individual industry stock portfolio, our stock investment has inferior return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>image test</title>
      <link>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2015/05/image-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ysyheidi.github.io/2015/05/image-test/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tranquilpeak integrate a unique &amp;ldquo;cover image&amp;rdquo; feature. Open this post to see how this feature sublimate your article.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>